博阿·兰道夫  你是个变态
Beau Randolph, you're a creep!
你是个败类
You're a loser!
你传播垃圾  你是个人渣
You peddle smut! You're scum!
你的人生一无是处
Your whole life adds up to nothing!
我向大家介绍
Let me introduce you to the guy
让我们今晚共聚一堂的人
who's the reason we're all here.
请欢迎我的朋友
Please give it up for my friend
"疯狂女大学生"的创办人
and the founder of "College Girls Gone Crazy"--
博阿·兰道夫
Beau Randolph!
谢谢你  特洛伊
Thank you, Troy.
欢迎各位来到这个你将铭记终生的夜晚
And welcome, all of you, to what I know will be a night to remember.
请各位享受音乐
So enjoy the music,
尽情畅饮
the free drinks.
欢迎各位捧场
And thank you for being a part
"疯狂女大学生  美女占领曼哈顿"之夜
of "College Girls Gone Crazy: Girls Take Manhattan"!
好啦  大家一起疯狂吧
All right. Let's get crazy!
要再来一杯吗  兰道夫先生
Another drink, Mr. Randolph?
我不是来开心的
I'm not here to party.
今晚不是
Not tonight.
那么下次吧
Maybe next time, then.
我觉得没有下次了
I don't think there's gonna be a next time.
不  不
Oh, no! No!
理查德
Richard,
我最后一招瑜伽"挺尸式"都被你毁了
you just ruined my final savasana.
如果你在进行方法派创作
If you are method writing
扮演你笔下凶案的被害人
and playing the role of your murder victim,
麻烦你死得安静点
could you please die a little bit more quietly?
谢谢
Thank you.
不  妈  我没有...
No, mother, I didn't--
我只是  我刚才
I just--I was...
我在谷歌我自己
I was googling... myself
我发现了这个
and I found this.
我不知道阿丽克西斯有自己的网站
Oh, I didn't know Alexis had a web site.
我也不知道
Neither did I.
这是个视博  视频博客
It's a vlog. It's a video blog.
好吧  很好啊
Oh, well, that's charming.
不  这不好
No. No, it is not charming.
今晚我和麦克斯去洛克菲勒中心溜冰
So tonight Max and I went ice skating
又一次
at Rockefeller Center again.
当然  我又一次假装溜得不稳
And, yes, I pretended to be unsteady on my skates again.
当然  麦克斯在我又一次要摔倒时抱住了我
And, yes, Max caught me as I "fell" again.
真是太可爱了
That is completely adorable,
她好上镜
and the camera just loves her.
当然了  那是我的基因
Of course, she gets that from me.
妈  阿丽克西斯对着全世界
Mother, Alexis is sharing,
分享她的私生活
with the whole world,
听好了  是她个人的
Mind you, personal,
她生活的私密细节
intimate details about her life--
她去了哪里  和谁一起去
Where she goes, who she goes with.
这可不安全
This is not safe.
亲爱的  你什么时候变得如此唠叨守旧了
Darling, when did you get to be such a fuddy-duddy?
相信我  你年轻的时候要糟得多
Believe me, you were far worse in your day.
我年轻的时候不是现在
My day is not today.
当时可不是现在
That day is not today.
现在流行网络跟踪狂
Today is the day of the internet stalker.
现在流行...
Today is the day for--
亲爱的  你还是接电话吧
Darling, why don't you just answer your phone?
瞧  贝克特打来的
Oh, and it's Beckett.
也许她有个不错的谋杀案可以把你
Maybe she has a nice murder to distract you
从父亲偏执狂中解救出来
from your parental paranoia.
有礼了
Namaste.
她有个视频博客  那又怎样  卡塞尔
So she video blogs, Castle. So what?
她这个年纪的人大多都有
Plenty of people do her age.
怎么了  她上传了不雅视频吗
Why? Did she post something inappropriate?
不  但重点不是这个
No, but that's not the point.
那重点是什么
Well, what is the point?
重点是  她分享过度了
The point is, she's oversharing.
她没有意识到  一旦传上互联网
She doesn't realize, whatever she posts on the internet
就永远公之于众了
is out there forever.
至少你可以感到高兴  阿丽克西斯没有
Well, at least be happy that Alexis isn't posting
-上传这样的东西  -《疯狂女大学生》
- something like that. - "College Girls Gone Crazy"?
对  打造出这个的是过度分享高手
Yeah, brought to you by the master of oversharing,
博阿·兰道夫先生
Mr. Beau Randolph.
她...
She...
想看就看吧  卡塞尔
It's all right to look, Castle.
看什么
Look at what?
看起来博阿·兰道夫的世界
So it doesn't seem as though Beau Randolph's world
在我们向他调查冰冻头案件后
has changed very much since we interviewed him
没什么改变嘛
for that frozen head case.
除了他不再置身其中
Except that he's no longer in it.
博阿·兰道夫是被害人吗
Beau Randolph is our victim?
他是在女卫生间遇害的吗
He was murdered in the women's bathroom?
"疯狂女大学生"又有新含义
Brings new meaning to "College Girls Gone Crazy."
看来是的
Looks that way.
他的尸体是在一个厕所隔间被发现的
His body was found in one of the stalls.
是被勒死的
Cause of death is strangulation.
徒手还是绳带类
Manual or ligature?
绳带类
Ligature.
看他脖子上的勒痕
Look at these bruises on his neck.
是胸罩上的扣环印
It's from a clasp on a bra.
凶器就被扔在他身旁
The murder weapon was found lying next to him.
我猜是一个女生将他引诱到这里幽会
I figure that a chick lured him in here for a little tryst
然后勒死了他
and then choked him out.
死亡时间
Time of death?
11点50分左右  他还在跟酒保说话
Well, he was talking to the bartender around 11:50,
11点58分尸体在隔间里被发现
and the body was found in the stall at 11:58 p.m.
蕾妮  你认为我们
Lanie, do you think that
能在凶器上获得DNA吗
we can get D.N.A. off of the murder weapon?
我已经采集了样本  但是看看这个
I already collected samples, but check this out.
这可是36D的苏特拉
This is a 36D Sultura.
高级货啊
Oh, that's high-end.
绝对的  一个要花上两百到两百五十块
Definitely. One of these could run you $200, $250.
两百五十美元买一个胸罩
$250 for a bra?
这钱花在运动鞋上就没问题了吧
Oh, but it's okay to spend that on a pair of sneakers, right?
运动鞋是很有实用性的
A pair of sneakers is practical.
明白吗  它们可以给予你...
Okay? They can support your, um...
驱逐出场
Eject.
出售这种胸罩的商店不会太多
The list of shops that sell that can't be that long
你去查查购买人是谁
so see if you can figure out who purchased it.
看来俱乐部的确有今晚的宾客名单
Hey, so looks like there was a guest list at the club tonight.
但如果你是一个兜里有20块钱的男人
But if you were a guy with 20 bucks in your pocket
出现在俱乐部门口
and you showed up at the door,
或是一位美女  都能进来
Or a pretty girl, you got in.
证人呢  有谁看到博阿和谁在一起吗
What about witnesses? Anyone see who Beau was with?
还没问到  不过警员已经带这里的人
Not yet, but uniforms are taking witness statements
回警局录口供了
from people here and down at the precinct.
他们今晚为网站拍摄视频
They were shooting for the web site tonight,
如果没有人看到博阿
so even if no one saw Beau,
也许有摄像机拍到他
chances are someone caught him on video.
谁负责拍摄
Who was in charge of taping?
制片人名叫特洛伊·斯特里兰德
The video's producer, a guy named Troy Strickland.
但更大的问题是  凶手是怎么
But the bigger question is how anyone got to Beau
接近博阿的
in the first place.
据俱乐部保安说  他今晚带了个保镖
According to club security, he came with a bodyguard tonight.
还真管用啊
Well, that worked out, didn't it?
埃斯波  你和莱恩去找保镖
Okay, Espo, you and Ryan take the bodyguard.
卡塞尔和我去跟制片人谈谈
Castle and I will talk to the producer.
世界上最差的保镖呢
So where's the world's worst bodyguard?
告诉保安通知他在警戒线这和我们会面
Told security to have him meet us near the rope line.
他叫琼斯
His name is Jones.
这人吗
This guy?
你是琼斯吗
You Jones?
我是琼斯  斯嘉丽·琼斯
I'm Jones. Scarlet Jones.
纽约警局的莱恩和埃斯波西托警探
Detectives Ryan and Esposito. NYPD.
你本该看着博阿的
You were supposed to have eyes on Beau.
怎么回事
So what happened?
博阿告诉我在车附近等着
Beau told me to wait outside with the car.
老板吩咐了  你就得照办
When your boss gives you a directive, you follow it.
但的确古怪
But it was weird.
他今晚好像不想让我进去
Like he didn't want me in there tonight.
他进俱乐部后你就没见过他了吗
So you never saw him again after he went in the club?
是的
I'm afraid not.
今晚你有看见可疑人员吗
Did you see anyone else that seemed suspicious tonight?
我做了威胁评估
Look, I did my threat assessment, okay?
唯一的威胁是...
The only one was, uh...
什么
What?
蒂芙尼  蒂芙尼·肖
Tiffany. Tiffany Shaw.
是那个女演员吧
Hey, that's that actress. Right?
她拍三级片...我是听说的
She does soft-core, cable type of... so I've heard.
她也是博阿的前女友
That's also Beau's ex-girlfriend.
两个月前  他想甩了她
He tried to dump her two months ago,
但是她不同意
but she wouldn't take no for an answer.
他申请了禁令
He got a restraining order against her,
但那还是没法甩掉她
and that still didn't keep her away.
她今晚也在这里吗
And she was here tonight?
她想进入俱乐部
She tried to get into the club,
我在门口拦住了她
and I stopped her at the rope line.
我告诉她  如果她不走
I told her I would call the police
我就叫警察  然后她就走了
if she didn't walk away, so she did.
她可能回来吗
Any chance she came back?
我没看到
Not through me.
但是我守不住每扇门
But I couldn't cover every door.
我认识蒂芙尼很久了
Yeah, I've known Tiffany for a long time.
她是个疯女人
She's a crazy chick,
而且深深爱上了博阿
and definitely obsessed with Beau.
但我今晚没在俱乐部见到她
But I didn't see her in the club tonight.
你注意到什么了吗  任何情况
What did you see, if anything?
只是漂亮姑娘  还有美式享乐
Uh, just pretty girls and good, clean, all-American fun.
天啊  真是受不了
Man, this sucks.
从一开始  我就和博阿合作
I've been with Beau since the beginning.
我是他的第一摄影师
I was his first cameraman,
第一制片人
first producer.
我们都不知道自己在做什么
We barely knew what we were doing.
他有家人吗
Did he have any family?
没有  他很小的时候妈妈就走了
No, his mom left when he was little.
他不知道爸爸是谁
He never knew his dad.
我觉得这是他的动力
I think it's what drove him.
这家公司就是他未曾有过的家庭
You know, this company was the family he never had.
人们觉得他是花花公子
People thought he was this sleaze,
身边总有一群女人
surrounding himself with all these women,
但这是因为他在寻找不曾拥有的温暖
but it's because he was looking for something he couldn't find.
特洛伊  我们得看看
Troy, we're gonna need to see
你今晚拍摄的录像
the footage that you shot tonight.
-上面可能有证据  -特洛伊
- There might be evidence on it. - Troy.
好  都拿去吧
Yeah, whatever you-- whatever you want.
加里
Hey, Gary.
哥们
Hey, man.
兄弟  我一听到消息就赶来了
I got down here as soon as I heard, buddy.
太可怕了
It's just so awful.
贝克特警探  卡塞尔先生
Uh, detective Beckett, Mr. Castle,
这是首席运营官加里·摩尔
this is Gary Moore, our C.O.O.
我去给你们拿录像
Uh, I'll go get that footage for you.
你们知道是谁杀的吗
Look, do you--do you have any idea who did this?
目前我们在调查蒂芙尼·肖
Right now we're looking into Tiffany Shaw.
你觉得还有谁
Is there anyone else that you think
可能想伤害博阿
might have wanted to harm Beau?
不幸的是
Well, unfortunately,
他每天都会收到死亡威胁
he received death threats on a daily basis.
谁寄来的
From whom?
保守人士  愤怒的男友
Moral crusaders, um, angry boyfriends,
愤怒的父亲
angry fathers...
后悔上过镜头的女人们
women who had second thoughts about being in our videos.
你们对这些威胁有记录吗
Did you keep track of these threats?
有  办公室里有个数据库
Yeah, we have a database back at our offices.
带我们过去
We'll need you to take us there.
"屌查"进行的如何
How's the in-breast-igation going?
所以你还是单身
And that's why you're still single.
我刚和蒂芙尼·肖的公关通了电话
So I just got off the phone with Tiffany Shaw's P.R. Rep.
她不仅穿的是36D的罩杯  和凶器一样
Not only does she wear a 36D like our murder weapon,
而且他们不知道她在哪
but they can't locate her.
我也不知道
Well, neither can I.
到目前为止  特洛伊给我们的录像中
So far she's not in any of this footage
没有发现她
that we got from Troy.
老实告诉你
To tell you the truth,
俱乐部的卫生间里太淫乱
what happens in those club bathrooms,
那件胸罩可能是别人脱的
that bra could've been left behind by anyone.
我们还有一百多份口供要录
Yeah, and we still got over a hundred statements to take.
整晚都得待这里了
We're gonna be here all night.
也许不用
Well, maybe not.
快看  那是博阿
Look. Check it out. It's Beau.
看见了吗
You--you see that?
他转过头
He--he turns his head
好像看到了什么
like he sees something
或是什么人
or someone.
那时是11点50
And it's at 11:50.
正是谋杀发生之前
That's right around the time of the murder.
看
Look.
他从那些女人身边走过去  她们看着他离去
He walks right by those women. They're watching him go.
等等
Wait a minute.
穿粉色的女孩
The girl in pink...
她来了  她看见博阿去了哪里
She's here. She saw where Beau went.
那是我
Yeah, that's me.
我本来不想去
I-I didn't want to go,
但是一个女友非得拉着我
but one of my girlfriends dragged me out.
现在我身陷谋杀案当中
Now I'm stuck in the middle of all this.
总比被谋杀的好
Better than in the middle.
在他被害之前  你看到他去了哪里
You saw where he went just before he was murdered.
你可能是最后一个看见他还活着的人
You might have been the last person to see him alive.
梅菲尔德女士  他从你身边经过时
Ms. Mayfield, when he walked by you,
你看见他要去哪里或者在干什么吗
Did you see where he was going or what he was doing?
灯光晃眼  很难看清
The lights were flashing. It was pretty hard to see.
对不起  我以前从没见过他
I'm sorry. I've never even seen the guy before.
这里平时有保安值班吗
Is there usually a guard on duty?
有  他六点下班
Well, yeah, he-- he leaves at 6:00,
但我们仍能用他的工作站
but we can still access our database
登陆数据库
from his workstation here.
重点看过去六个月
Okay, I'd like to focus on all of the threats
有没有什么威胁
from the last six months or so.
这是登陆日志吗
Is this an entry log?
是的  怎么了
Uh, yes. Why?
这里显示博阿·兰道夫
It says that Beau Randolph
凌晨12点09分扫过出入证
swiped his key card at 12:09 a.m.
不可能啊  他那时早已经死了
That's impossible. He was already dead.
凶手偷了出入证
Our killer stole the card
进入这栋大楼
and then gained entry into this building.
为了什么
What were they after?
根据日志来看
According to this,
用这张出入证的人进了博阿的办公室
whoever used that key card went into Beau's office.
办公室里有摄像头吗
Are there security cameras in there?
正在调监控录像出来
Pulling it up now.
是冲着保险箱去的
He's going for the safe.
博阿刚装上
Beau just had that installed.
里面都放了些什么
What does he keep in there?
不清楚
I don't know,
但一提到那个保险箱  他就
but when it came to that safe, he was...
神经兮兮的
pretty paranoid.
是张记忆卡
That's an S.D. card.
快回头
Come on. Turn around.
天呐
Oh, my God.
是博阿·兰道夫的保镖
That's Beau Randolph's bodyguard.
她做事可真不靠谱啊
Well, she's not very good at her job.
好消息是
Good news is,
斯嘉丽·琼斯不是世上最烂的保镖
Scarlet Jones is not the world's worst bodyguard.
坏消息是  她是杀人凶手
Bad news is, she's a murderer.
这么性感的人锒铛入狱
Someone that sexy going to prison?
这本身就是种犯罪
That in itself is a crime.
有必要吗
Is this really necessary?
我已经对你们的警探知无不言了
I told your detectives everything I know.
未必吧
Not everything.
比如说  你没告诉我们
For instance, you didn't tell us
你才为兰道夫先生工作了
that you had been working for Mr. Randolph
几周时间而已
for only a couple of weeks.
有什么关系
How is that relevant?
你的口供里提到
Well, in your statement, you said that
博阿进俱乐部时  你在车里等他
when Beau went into the club, you stayed with the limo.
是的  没错
That's right. That's what I did.
那也许你能解释一下这个
So then maybe you can explain this.
照片里貌似是你在偷记忆卡
That appears to be you stealing an S.D. card.
在你说"邪恶双胞胎姐妹"之前  要知道
And before you say "evil twin", just know--
那借口太老套了
it's been done.
他刚死你就用他的出入证
You broke in to his office just after he died
闯进了他的办公室
using his key card.
你怎么拿到出入证的
How did you get it?
我没杀博阿
Look, I didn't kill Beau,
更不是为了他的出入证
and certainly not for his key card.
他落在车里了  我知道这是我唯一的机会
He left it in the limo. I knew it was my only chance.
什么叫唯一的机会
What do you mean, only chance?
有段性爱录像
There was this... sex tape.
我朋友犯了个错  跟博阿上了床
This friend of mine made the mistake of sleeping with Beau,
他把过程录了下来
and he videotaped it.
她知道要是泄露出去
She knew that if it ever got out,
她一生就毁了
it would destroy her life,
于是我做他保镖  保证录像不会泄露
so I took this job to make sure the tape never got out.
博阿叫我待在车里时
When Beau told me to stay with the car,
我知道这是我唯一的机会
I knew it was my only shot,
所以我闯入了他的办公室
so, yes, I-I broke in to his office,
我把记忆卡偷走毁掉了
I took the S.D. card, and I destroyed it.
但仅此而已
But that's all I did.
你朋友叫什么
And who is this friend of yours?
明蒂·诺顿
Her name is Mindy Norton.
正如我跟那两位警探说的  凶手一定是蒂芙尼
Like I told your detectives, the killer must be Tiffany.
她恨博阿跟她分手
She hated Beau for breaking up with her.
她一定是趁我不在
Look, she-- she must have snuck back into the club
偷偷溜回了俱乐部
while I was gone.
我们看过监控录像
We reviewed the video footage.
没有证据显示蒂芙尼当晚在夜店
There's no evidence Tiffany was at the club.
事实上  所有证据都指向你
In fact, all of the evidence points to you.
博阿是11点50分之后死的
Beau died after 11:50.
这点时间足够让你杀了他
That gave you enough time to kill him,
偷走记忆卡  再回到俱乐部
take the S.D. card, and get back to the club.
不  我11点45分出发去博阿的办公室
No, I left for Beau's office at 11:45.
泊车员看到我开车走的
The valets saw me drive off.
我跟你们说  我没杀人
I am telling you, somebody else did this.
不是蒂芙尼的话  那么
And if it wasn't Tiffany, then...
也许我知道是谁
I think I might know who.
上周在市中心有个人
Last week there was this guy in midtown.
在大街上袭击了博阿
He practically attacked Beau in the street,
他说会让博阿为自己所做的一切
saying that he would make Beau pay
付出代价
for whatever it was he did.
你知道这人是谁吗
Do you know who this guy was?
不知道  但他冲到博阿面前
No, but he got in Beau's face.
还向他大吼大叫
And he was yelling at Beau,
说博阿出卖了他
saying that he had double-crossed him.
他动起手来  于是我介入了
He got physical, so I, uh, stepped in.
然后呢
And then what?
打断了他的鼻子  打断了几根肋骨
Broke his nose and a couple of ribs, I think.
听见了吗  她打断了他的鼻子
Oh, did you hear that? She broke his nose.
那又如何
Yeah, so?
太火辣了
So... that's hot.
我不认识你
Who are you?
你完全不认识他
And you have no idea who he is?
不认识  不过再见的话我能认出来
No, but I'd know if I saw him again.
斯嘉丽的朋友明蒂证实了
So... Scarlet's friend Mindy confirmed her story
性爱录像的说法
about the sex tape.
还有两个泊车员看到她在11点45离开俱乐部
Plus two of the valets saw her leave the club at 11:45.
她的不在场证明应该成立
So it looks like her alibi is checking out.
你好像特别开心
You know, you seem unusually happy about this.
没啊  就是
No, I'm just, you know--
办案子嘛
you know, working the case.
说到案子
Speaking of which,
我们还在找蒂芙尼·肖
we're still trying to track down Tiffany Shaw,
但目前还没发现
but no luck so far.
同时  斯嘉丽正在跟画师描述
Meantime, Scarlet's working with a sketch artist
袭击博阿的人
on Beau's attacker.
画好了传到医院急诊室去
When it's done, send it off to hospital emergency rooms.
要是她真像自己说的把人打成那样
If she did as much damage as she claims,
他应该会去就医
then he would've sought medical attention.
那我去看看素描画得怎么样了
I should probably go see how the sketch is coming along.
去吧
Yeah, you do that.
我一直在看
So I've been working through
博阿·兰道夫办公室的恐吓数据库
the threat database from Beau Randolph's office.
有什么发现吗
Did anything pop?
有  这个叫罗纳德·阿姆斯特朗的人
Yeah. One guy. Ronald Armstrong.
"体面之声"的创始人
Founder of Voices for Decency.
是不是一直上电视的那个
Is that the guy that's on TV all the time,
一直推动媒体集团和社区商业
the one that's pushing a conservative agenda
保守化的人
on media groups and community businesses?
是他  就是他
Yeah, that's him. He's the one
就是在俱乐部门口组织示威的人
who organized the protest outside the nightclub.
是吗  有没有证据显示他有暴力倾向
Really? Any reason to believe that he's violent?
这是阿姆斯特朗
Well, here is a quote
在网站上给粉丝的回复
from Armstrong on his web site to his followers.
"我们的职责就是消灭污秽的传播者"
"Our work is to rid the nation of the purveyors of filth."
"如果博阿·兰道夫听不到我们的声音
"If Beau Randolph doesn't heed our voices,
他就会看到我们的怒火"
he must fall to our wrath."
但这能说明他是嫌疑人吗
But does that make him a suspect?
也许不是他亲自动手
Well, maybe not him personally,
两周前阿姆斯特朗又一次
but two weeks ago, Armstrong organized
在兰道夫的公寓外组织了一场示威
another protest outside Beau Randolph's loft.
砸了他家窗户  烧了他的照片
Windows were broken. Beau was burned in effigy.
闹得很凶
It got pretty ugly.
就是昨晚示威的那一帮人
Those same protesters were outside the nightclub last night.
兰道夫先生的死就像他的生活
Mr. Randolph's death was like his life--
粗俗
vulgar...
令人作呕
offensive.
看看我们国家成了什么样
Look what's become of our nation.
事实上就是他这种人为了谋求利益
The truth is that the Beau Randolphs of this world
丑化了我们的文化  侮辱了我们的人民
profit by degrading our culture and everyone in it.
我不会因为捍卫道德观而道歉
I don't apologize for defending moral values.
问题是  捍卫起来你会做到什么地步
The question is, how far would you go to defend them?
你最近组织的那次示威
You recently led a protest against him
以暴力收场
that turned violent.
我的几个兄弟有点太热血了
A few of my brethren became a bit overzealous,
仅此而已
That's all.
也许是你出言鼓励
Maybe your words gave them encouragement.
别搞错了  我们在战斗
Make no mistake. We are at war.
但我只组织好人为他们的原则而战
But I simply ask good people to stand up for their principles
用法律手段寻求改变
and to use any and all legal means to force change.
我需要昨晚在俱乐部门口示威的
I will need the names of all of the protesters
所有人的名字
that were at the club last night.
那我谢绝您的请求
And I respectfully decline your request.
我们能拿到搜查令
We can get a warrant.
深表怀疑
I doubt it.
但祝你好运
But good luck to you.
谢谢你的咖啡
Thanks for the coffee.
就是他找过博阿麻烦吗
So this is the guy that came after Beau?
如果我知道他会再动手
Yeah. If I knew he was coming back,
就不会只打断他鼻子了
I'd have broken more than just his nose.
昨晚在俱乐部
Hey, look, um, about last night at the club...
我很抱歉  我太过分了
I'm sorry. I was-- I was way out of line.
我也是
Yeah. So was I.
我应该告诉你们所有的事
I should've come clean with you guys about everything.
再见
See ya.
See you later.
斯嘉丽
Hey, Scarlet.
能一起喝一杯吗
Do you think maybe we could get a drink later?
现在你不是嫌疑人了
I mean, now that you're not a suspect anymore...
你天天就干这个啊
So this is what you do all day.
悠闲吧
Right?
不  这是工作
No, it's work. That's...
这次的案子
That's a case.
我知道  逗你玩呢
I know. I was just messing with you.
你想见我
Uh, so you wanted to see me?
阿丽克西斯  我发现了你的视博
So, Alexis, I, um... I found your vlog,
很可爱
and while it is super cute, um--
奶奶告诉我了
Yeah, gram told me.
你觉得我会被不怀好意的人利用
You think I'm catnip for predators online.
人应该  特别是女性应该
I-it's just, people have to be, and especially women,
注意不要对外面世界暴露太多
need to be leery about how much they put out into the world.
我不想看到你以后会因为一时兴起
I don't want to see you haunted for years
放到网上的东西而苦恼
by something you posted on a whim.
爸  你把我说的跟视频里的女孩一样
Dad, you're acting like I'm one of these girls
会为了免费的酒露点
who flashes the camera for a free shot of tequila.
那只是个视博
It's just a silly vlog.
里面都是个人信息
With personal information.
万一被坏人看到呢
What if the wrong person sees it?
你一直叫我出去看看
You're always pushing me to get out there,
体验生活  玩得开心  但你却不愿意信任我
experiment, have fun, but you refuse to trust me.
阿丽克西斯
Okay, Alexis--
爸爸  我不想再跟你说这件事了
Dad, I'm not having this conversation with you.
我得走了  还有课
I've got to go. I've got class.
没事  我马上走
No, stay. I'm leaving.
想跟我说说吗
Anything you want to talk about?
不用了
No. No.
不
No.
卡塞尔  看这里
Castle, over here.
不  不  看
No, no, look.
这是斯嘉丽说的那个人
It's the guy from Scarlet's sketch.
找博阿麻烦的那个人
It's the man who attacked Beau.
看他的鼻子
Look at his nose.
就是斯嘉丽打的
That's from Scarlet hitting him.
那晚他就在俱乐部
He was at the club last night,
也许是继续未尽的事业
Probably to finish the job.
我可以告诉你们他的名字  赛斯·帕里诺
And I can tell you his name--Seth Parrino.
我刚给布朗克斯区综合医院的急诊室打过电话
Just got off the phone with an E.R. nurse at Bronx General.
帕里诺因为鼻骨和肋骨骨折
Parrino was treated and released
进了医院进行了治疗
for a nasal fracture and some bruised ribs.
还知道什么情况
What do we know about him?
他总和暴力扯上关系
Well, he was no stranger to violence.
三年前因敲诈被判刑
He was convicted of racketeering three years ago.
知道他现在在哪儿吗
You know where we can find him?
敲诈人的帕里诺还能有进口公司
Racketeering and Parrino owns an import business?
我只有五个字要说  贝克特
I've got two words for you, Beckett--
维托·柯里昂[教父电影中的教父]
Vito Corleone.
准确的来说  那是名字不是字
Technically, those are names, not words.
如果博阿·兰道夫曾欺骗过黑手党
If Beau Randolph double-crossed a member of the Mafia...
那就难怪会死翘翘了
no wonder he got whacked.
你这推断也太离谱了
That is rampant speculation.
那是我的专长
Rampant speculation is my specialty.
如果博阿·兰道夫拍过
What if Beau Randolph produced a video
黑手党老大女儿的"影像作品"呢
featuring the daughter of a Mafia boss,
胸罩就变成了黑手党
and the brassiere became the Mafia's, uh,
特殊的绞喉用具了
garrote du jour?
帕里诺进出口公司
禁止停车
你可以闭嘴了
You can stop talking now.
赛斯·帕里诺
Seth Parrino.
你们干什么
What the hell are you doing?
你们不能进来
You can't be in here.
纽约警局  有几个问题要问你
NYPD. We have a few questions.
或许不止是问几个问题而已
Maybe more than just a few questions.
《疯狂男大学生》  不是吧
"College Guys Gone Nuts," really?
对  对  这商标是我的
Yeah, yeah, and I own the trademark,
-所以你就别动脑筋了  -该死
- so don't get any ideas. - Rats.
这里的人都满18岁了  我也有许可证
Look, everybody here is over 18, and I have my permits.
我们不是来查你的舞者的  帕里诺先生
We're not here about your dancers, Mr. Parrino.
是吧
Are we?
对  不是
Right. No.
我们是来了解博阿·兰道夫的事
We're here about Beau Randolph.
好吧  我们起了分歧
Okay, yeah, yeah, we had a falling out.
我没杀他
I didn't kill anybody.
因为什么起了分歧
A falling out about what?
这个  《疯狂男大学生》
This. "College Guys Gone Nuts."
几个月前
A couple months ago,
我去拉他入伙
I approached him about partnering up.
把他的节目性别倒过来
You know, maybe do for women what he did for men.
你们能想象这商业前景吗
Can you imagine the merchandising possibilities,
可以出DVD  网络视频  电子游戏
DVDs, internet, video games.
开始他还答应来着
You know, at first he said he was in.
可突然间
Then all of a sudden, boom.
我还没反应过来  他就改变主意了
Just like that, changes his mind.
不明原因吗
Can't imagine why.
博阿是个有卓见的人  这点我承认
Beau was a visionary. I grant him that.
他是个有卓见的人
He was a visionary.
可出于某种原因  他就是...
But, uh, for some reason, he just--
他就是不明白  你们懂吗
He--he couldn't-- couldn't see it, you know?
我懂  你说得对
I get it. You're right.
就像是风能  太阳能
I mean, it's like wind power. It's, uh, solar energy.
就是这样
Exactly.
没错
Yeah.
我被打那天
Day this happened,
我发现他准备退出
I found out he was gonna back out on the deal.
说他准备投资
Said he's gonna-- he's gonna invest
其它项目
in something else--
儿童项目  或类似的玩意儿
Oh, kids programming or something like that.
好像我不知道他就是要打发我
Like I couldn't tell he was just blowing me off.
然后他让那保镖打我
And then he sics that bodyguard on me.
你那晚为什么去俱乐部
Why did you go to the club that night?
我试图做最后的努力
I was trying to make a final pitch.
再给他一次机会
You know, give him one more chance to--
答应和我合伙  再给发疯一次机会
to--to say yes, one more chance to go nuts.
我想他拒绝了
I take it he said no.
我还没机会问  他就死了
Oh, I never got a chance to ask.
我从后面跑去找他
I ran into him in the back,
他当时正在和某个女孩吵架
and he was having a fight with some chick.
场面很激烈
It looked nasty.
我想当时不是时候
I just, I figured, you know, it wasn't the time.
当时几点
And when was this?
11点半左右吧
God, like 11:30 or so.
11点半
11:30?
你能描述一下这个女人吗
Do you think you could describe this woman?
可以  她头发是短棕色的
Yeah, yeah, yeah, she has, uh... short brown hair,
身材很辣
Smokin' hot body.
对了  她嘴唇上方有颗痣
Oh, and she had a mole right over her lip.
就是她  赛斯·帕里诺的神秘女人
Here she is-- Seth Parrino's mystery woman.
好  把她的照片发给派对组织方
All right, send her photo to the party organizers.
看看是否有人认得出
See if anyone recognizes her.
没必要
No need.
看她那颗痣
Check out that mole.
眼熟吗
Look familiar?
这么说  博阿的前女友
So Beau's ex-girlfriend
蒂芙尼·肖当时在场
Tiffany Shaw was there.
她一定是乔装打扮后
She must have disguised herself,
趁斯嘉丽离开后偷溜进了俱乐部
then slipped in to the club after Scarlet left.
发逮捕令抓她
Get out a warrant on her.
能让莱恩去吗
You think we could have Ryan do that?
我还有约
I have plans.
是吗  谁啊
Really? Do these plans have a name?
我擦  你不是吧
Oh, shut up. You didn't.
她把人鼻子给打断了  想象一下性爱场面吧
She broke a guy's nose. You know she's gotta be freaky.
拜托
Come on.
你去哪里
Hey, where you going?
别问了  有进展吗
Don't ask. You got anything?
没想到我在读完六年级后
Well, um... I never thought I'd say this
还会说这些话
after graduating the sixth grade,
我们在进行文胸调查
but our bra research is in.
发现六个女人买的苏特拉牌文胸
Turns out six women purchased a Sultura bra
大小和款式和凶器相同
identical to the size and model of our murder weapon
都是在上东区同一家内衣店买的
from the same upper east side lingerie shop--
店名叫欲望
Carnal Desires.
这六个人中  有一个很显眼
Of the six, one name stood out.
-蒂芙尼·肖  -越来越明朗了
- Tiffany Shaw. - It gets better.
显然她把自己的弄丢了
Apparently she must have lost hers,
因为她今早给店里打电话
because she called the shop this morning
问是不是还有库存
to see if they had another one in stock.
她这时候正在去取件的路上
She's on her way in to get it right now.
她旧的还在这里
You know, it seems like such a shame
我们就害她只好去买新的  还真是不好意思
to have her buy a new one when her old one is right here.
天呐  我的文胸
Oh, my god. My bra.
太感谢了
Thank you so much.
你们在哪里找到的
Where did you guys find this?
绕在博阿·兰道夫的脖子上
Wrapped around Beau Randolph's neck,
把他给勒死了
strangling him to death.
等等  你们该不会以为
Wait. You guys don't think
我和他的死有关吧
that I had anything to do with this, do you?
凶器是你的
The murder weapon belongs to you.
死者有对你的禁令
Our victim had a restraining order against you.
而你那晚又执意要见他
And you were so determined to get to see him that night
你换了身装扮  躲过安保
that you changed your appearance in order to get past security.
不是你们想的那样
It's not what you think.
听着  我只是想跟他说话
Look, I just wanted to talk to him.
我们俩是灵魂伴侣
The two of us were soul mates.
几个月前  他变了
And then a couple of months ago, he changes.
变得很严肃  很偷偷摸摸
He got so serious, so secretive.
后来冷不丁他就甩了我
And then out of the blue, he just dumps me
没有原因
for no reason.
我只想知道原因
I just wanted to know why.
我有权知道原因
I deserved to know why.
于是你去俱乐部
So you went to the club
和他对峙
to confront him.
你猜他说了什么
And do you know what he said?
他说我不是他与之共度余生的那种人
He said that I wasn't the kind of person that he could be with anymore.
好像他是圣人一样
Like he's such a saint.
然后他说  如果我再出现
And then he said if I showed up again,
他就报警抓我
he'd have me arrested.
这话够狠的  你一定很生气吧
That's pretty harsh. That must have made you angry.
这还用问  我当然生气
Damn right, it made me angry.
我想好好收拾他一顿
I wanted to hurt him so bad.
所以你就去了洗手间
So you went into the bathroom...
杀了他
and then you killed him.
什么
Wh-what?
你杀了他
You killed him.
不  我可没杀他
Whoa. Okay. No, I didn't kill him.
你刚才说你要好好收拾他
You just said you wanted to hurt him so bad.
是的
Yeah,
所以我就随便找了人
so I grabbed the nearest guy
拉他进洗手间干了一炮  就当是报复
and pulled him into the bathroom for revenge sex.
那你的内衣怎么会
Then how did your bra end up
缠在博阿·兰道夫的脖子上呢
wrapped around Beau Randolph's neck?
我一定是落在洗手间里了
I must have left it in the bathroom.
你在夜店里干过那事吗  警探
You ever do it in a nightclub, detective,
"辣"得浑身是汗  还得快着点
Hot, sweaty, quick?
丢东西是正常的
Things go missing.
那人能证明你说的话吗
Can this guy confirm your story?
证明
Confirm it?
我很了解男人
I mean, knowing men,
他可能已经让整个东海岸的人都知道了
he's probably told the entire east coast already.
那么他叫什么
So what's his name?
你不知他的名字
You don't know his name.
那只是夜店里的一夜情
It was club sex.
我知道这很蠢
Look, I know it was stupid.
完事后我觉得糟透了  就离开了
Afterward, I felt awful, so I left.
那时是几点
And what time was that?
11点45分  你可以去问司机
11:45. You can call my driver.
我离开夜店的时候
And when I walked out of that club,
博阿还活着
Beau was still alive.
听我说  我比任何人都了解博阿
Look, I knew Beau better than anyone,
他一定遇到了什么事
and something wasn't right.
从他的眼神我就能看出来
I could see it in his eyes.
起初我以为他有了别的女人
At first I thought it was another woman,
所以我就跟踪他看看到底是谁
so I followed him to find out who it was.
但当我发现他保镖的真正目的后
But when I saw what that bodyguard of his was up to,
我就知道一定是什么大事
I knew it was something bigger.
她有什么目的
What was she up to?
肯定不是好事
Nothing good.
几个星期之前  我跟踪了她
A couple of weeks ago, I followed her.
她穿过了布赖恩特公园后
She was crossing Bryant park,
突然来到一个垃圾箱前
and suddenly, she reaches into a trash bin
取出来这个
and pulls out this--
一袋现金
a bag of cash.
斯嘉丽越来越神秘了
So the mystery of Scarlet deepens.
涉及到从垃圾箱取出一袋现金的杀人案
A dead drop involving a bag of cash and a trash bin,
她还让我们去追踪假线索
sending us after false leads at every turn--
这可是经典的间谍手段
This is classic spy craft.
但那些钱是谁给的  她又在为谁工作呢
But whose money is it and who is she really working for?
斯嘉丽前几份工作是为500强公司
Scarlet's last few jobs were doing high-level consulting
做高级顾问
for Fortune-500 companies.
这与给博阿·兰道夫当保镖可是天壤之别
That's a far cry from babysitting Beau Randolph.
可能她仍然在为某个公司工作
Maybe she's still working for one of them.
或许她的工作就是接近博阿
Maybe her job with Beau was just to get
以便完成她真正的任务
close enough to him to accomplish her real mission.
是啊  鬼知道那是什么
Yeah, whatever that was.
我刚跟斯嘉丽的朋友明蒂聊过
Hey, so I just spoke with Scarlet's friend Mindy.
在我跟她解释了
After I explained to her
什么是妨碍司法公正后
what obstruction of justice looks like,
她承认斯嘉丽给了她1000美元
she admitted that Scarlet paid her $1,000
让她为SD卡说辞打圆场
to vouch for that story about the SD card.
无论卡里存了什么
Whatever's on it,
肯定不是她和博阿的性爱录像
it's not a sex tape of her and Beau.
但那到底是什么
Okay, so what the hell is it
而她为什么迫不及待地想要得到呢
and why does she want it so bad?
我想我知道怎样找出事实真相
You know, I think I know how we can find out.
基本上是任何事
Pretty much everything.
你太强了
You're super strong.
我就说嘛
I'm just saying.
有什么事吗
Is everything okay?
没有  只是同事的电话
It's-- nah, it's just work.
看来有时他们离了我不行
It seems like they can't operate without me sometimes.
你懂的
You know how it is.
你是想再来一杯呢
So do you want to get another drink
还是去找个地方吃点东西
or maybe get a table and get some dinner?
去我那继续聊聊怎么样
How about we continue this conversation at my place?
好啊
Okay.
或者
Or...
更好一些
better yet...
去我那继续聊聊怎么样
why don't we continue this conversation back at my place?
她又性感
She's hot.
又能打  还是商业间谍
She kicks ass. She's a corporate spy.
天啊  她太完美了
Man, she is perfect.
她为什么要当坏人呢
Why'd she have to be the bad guy?
很抱歉我们把你"截鸡"  哥们
Sorry we had to cop block you, bro.
你知道这有多荒唐吗
You know this is ridiculous.
我跟博阿·兰道夫的死一点关系都没有
I had nothing to do with Beau Randolph's death.
我知道你没说实话
I also know that you lied to us.
我有不在场证据
I have an alibi.
那张SD卡上有什么  还有你在为谁工作
What was on the SD card and who do you work for?
我已经告诉过你了
I already told you.
你当保镖不是为了取回性爱录像
You didn't take that job to get back a sex tape.
你的朋友明蒂已经撤销了她的供词
and your friend Mindy already recanted her story.
我不相信博阿付薪酬的方式是
And I highly doubt that Beau paid you
把钱放在垃圾箱里
by leaving cash in a trash bin.
你还是别演戏了
So why don't you drop the act
告诉我到底发生了什么
and tell me what the hell is going on
还有那张卡上有什么
and what was on that card?
我不知道
I don't know.
-斯嘉丽  -我不知道
- Scarlet.  - I don't know.
你真觉得我会相信
Do you actually expect me to believe
你对你偷的卡上有什么内容一无所知吗
that you have no idea what was on the thing that you stole?
我只知道
All I know is that
博阿对那张卡非常在意  甚至疑神疑鬼
Beau was obsessed about it, paranoid.
所以我想那就是我的雇主想要的东西
So I figured it's exactly what my employer was looking for.
他们让你找什么东西
What did they send you to find?
丑闻
Dirt.
对博阿不利的证据
Uh, incriminating evidence they could use against Beau.
谁是你的雇主
Who? Who's your employer?
斯嘉丽  无论你说不说我都会查出来
Scarlet, I'm gonna find out whether you tell me or not,
除非你跟我们合作  否则如果他们
and if they were involved in Beau Rndolph's death,
跟博阿·兰道夫的死有关  你就是共犯
then that makes you an accomplice unless you help.
小青蛙公司
Little Frog Enterprises.
是小青蛙公司雇的我
I was hired by Little Frog Enterprises.
小青蛙公司  那个制作儿童节目的公司
Little Frog Enterprises, the children's media company?
这讲不通啊
That makes no sense.
博阿跟赛斯·帕里诺说过
Beau told Seth Parrino that he was investing
他在给儿童节目投资
in children's programming,
或许有些关联
So maybe it's related.
这又怎样  难道《摇摆尾》
So what, the folks behind "The Jigglewags"
和《欢乐玩偶秀》的制作人
and "Happy Polly's Puppet Playtime"
是杀死博阿的幕后黑手吗
are the people pulling the strings behind Beau's death?
我们能确定的是
Well, all we know for sure is that they were trying
他们想挖掘博阿的丑闻
to dig up some dirt on Beau.
这个男人生活中充满丑闻
The man's life was dirt.
他甚至都没有脱离金钱关系的炮友
He hardly had a sexual encounter he didn't try to monetize.
他们想找什么
What are they hoping to find?
还有  找到了又能怎样
And what were they planning on doing with it?
很抱歉  警探
I'm sorry, Detective,
但是你们找错人了
but, uh, you got the wrong guy.
我在正规的家庭娱乐公司工作
I, uh, I work in wholesome family entertainment,
不搞不正当行业
Not smut.
但你或是你们公司的人
And yet you or someone from your company
雇用了斯嘉丽·琼斯渗入博阿·兰道夫的公司
hired Scarlet Jones to infiltrate Beau Randolph's company
并暗中监视他
and spy on him.
我们猜想  作为公司创办者和总经理
We figured as founder and C.E.O.,
你可能知情
you might know something about that.
听着  你得理解
Look, you have to understand.
我建立这家公司是为了我的子女
I... I built this company for my children, okay,
我的子孙
for my grandchildren,
好让父母们不必担心
So parents wouldn't have to worry
孩子们接触到性和暴力
about their kids being exposed to sex and violence.
很抱歉  但这和博阿有什么关系呢
I'm sorry. What does this have to do with Beau?
我们公司发展得太快
We expanded too quickly.
大佬们对我们虎视眈眈
Sharks were circling.
六周前  博阿·兰道夫找到我
Six weeks ago, Beau Randolph approached me
说他可以帮我
and, uh, he said he could help.
他说他有丰厚的现金储备
He said he had large cash reserves
正在寻找投资机会
and he was looking to invest.
博阿为什么想要投资小青蛙公司呢
Why would Beau want to invest in Little Frog?
他说他不想
He said that, uh, he didn't want
让"疯狂女大学生"成为他的遗产
"College Girls Gone Crazy" to be his legacy.
他说他想做别的生意
He said he wanted to do more.
他看中了我们公司
He liked the company.
我猜想你不赞同他的提议
I take it you weren't interested.
当然  难道要让那家伙的肮脏名声
What, and let that guy's sleazy reputation
玷污我辛苦建立的一切吗
taint everything I worked so hard to build?
绝不  我知道他在盘算什么
No. I knew exactly what he was doing.
他想利用我们公司的名声
He was trying to use my company
为自己正名
to legitimize himself.
他想利用它来获取
He wanted to use it to obtain something
他自己无法获得的东西
he couldn't earn on his own.
什么东西
And what's that?
尊敬
Respect.
我拒绝他之后  他向董事会提议
After I said no, he took his proposal to the board.
董事会很欣赏他的提议
They seemed to like his offer.
我只想找到压制他的办法
I was just looking for some leverage.
我想令他退缩
I just needed something to make him back off.
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
考虑到你做过的这些事
'Cause given everything you've already done,
雇人溜进那个派对干掉他
it would've been easy to hire someone
简直是轻而易举
to slip into that party and just make it go away.
我和他的死无关
I had nothing to do with his death.
但我或许知道是谁干的
But I might know who did.
斯嘉丽
Scarlet...
说他无比看重这张记忆卡
said he guarded this SD card with his life.
现在我知道原因了
Now I know why.
我本想用这个对付兰道夫
I thought I could use it as leverage against Randolph,
但是
but, uh,
现在看来  很明显
well, now it's pretty clear
他曾用这个勒索过其他人
he was using it to blackmail someone else.
里面记录了什么东西
What's on it?
不是东西
It's not what.
是人
It's who.
这是一盘性爱录像带  那又如何
It's a sex tape. So what?
像博阿这样的家伙  这种录像多得是
A guy like Beau could have dozens of these.
录像带没什么  关键是那个女孩
It's not the tape. It's the girl.
我要看看她的脸
I need a shot of her face.
我们见过她
We know her.
夜总会里穿粉色衣服的女孩
That's the girl in pink from the nightclub.
是的  我们那晚录了她的口供
Yeah. We took her statement that night.
她说她不认识博阿
She said didn't know Beau.
我想她撒了谎
Well... I think she lied.
她叫什么名字
So what's her name?
坎迪斯·梅菲尔德  25岁
Candice Mayfield, 25.
根据你的记录
According to your report,
她正是在博阿·兰道夫死前
she is literally one of the last people
最后见过的几个人之一
to see Beau Randolph alive.
她有什么特别
Okay. So what's so special about her?
据我所知  没有
As far as I could see, nothing.
她是一名幼儿园教师
She's a kindergarten teacher.
无前科  没有什么特别的
No record. There's nothing extraordinary about her.
除了她父亲的身份
Except for maybe who her father is.
根据法庭文件
According to court documents
坎迪斯·梅菲尔德的真名是坎迪斯·阿姆斯特朗
Candice Mayfield's real name is Candice Armstrong--
罗纳德·阿姆斯特朗的女儿
Ronald Armstrong's daughter.
等等  是这个罗纳德·阿姆斯特朗吗
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. This Ronald Armstrong?
体面之音的创办者  罗纳德·阿姆斯特朗吗
The founder of Voices for Decency Ronald Armstrong?
对  是那个想打垮博阿的公司的人
Mm-hmm. The one who's trying to bring down Beau's company.
阿姆斯特朗的女儿用了她母亲
And Armstrong's daughter changed her name
娘家的姓氏来躲避丑闻
to her mom's maiden to get away from all the notoriety.
不过博阿发现她的真实身份
Only Beau found out who she really was.
因此博阿引诱她发生关系
So Beau lures her into a tawdry encounter,
把过程拍下来  并用录像来勒索她
films it, and then uses the video to blackmail her.
如果她不帮他劝服她父亲
And if she didn't agree to get her father off of his back,
博阿就将录像公诸于世
Beau was going to show the tape.
坎迪斯知道一旦录像流出
Candice knows that if that tape got out,
她的人生就毁了
it would ruin her life.
这会让她的家族蒙羞
It would embarrass her whole family.
博阿用录像带把她逼入绝境
Beau uses the video to push her into a corner.
除了反击  她别无选择
She has no choice but to push back.
她就是凶手
She's our killer.
你回家做什么呢
So what brings you home,
除了调制一份巨大无比的甜品之外
aside from concocting a ridiculously huge dessert?
顺便说一句  我是在夸你哦
Kudos, by the way.
我讨厌和你吵架
I hate it when we argue.
我也是
Me, too.
只是  我都18岁了
It's just, I'm 18.
我无需再事事征询你的同意
I don't have to ask for permission anymore.
不  我理解你
No, I know that.
我想让你像我一样体验生活
And I want you to experience things the way I did.
只是  如今时代不同了
It's just, things are different now.
这个案子让我明白
If this case has taught me anything, it's that...
当你把东西放到网上后
when you put something out there,
任何人都能看到
anyone can see it,
不管是面试官还是某个互联网恶人
from a future job interviewer to an internet creep.
你以为我不知道吗
You don't think I know that?
我们这一代生活在数字化环境中
My generation grew up in a digital fish bowl.
无论我们多小心翼翼
And no matter how careful we are,
隐私都会泄露出去
stuff will get out there.
朋友们在相册里圈我
You know, friends will tag me in photos,
难免做出些蠢事
inevitably doing something stupid.
干嘛让那些事定义我
Why should that define me?
干嘛不自己闯一闯  给自己下定义
Why can't I go out there and define myself?
不  我能理解  阿丽克西斯
No, I get it, Alexis. It's just that I w--
老爸  听着  我懂
Dad, look, I know.
我知道你想保护我  但是...
I know you want to keep me safe, but...
保护我的唯一方法就是给我绑上气泡包装
the only way to do that is wrap me in bubble wrap
藏到洞里
and hide me in a cave.
相信我
Believe me...
我考虑过那么做
I've thought about it.
问题是  阿丽克西斯
The thing is, Alexis,
外面的世界  坏人做着坏事
there are bad people out there who do bad things,
你暴露的东西越多
and the more you expose...
老爸  你了解我的
Dad, you know me.
我很小心
I'm careful
还很聪明
and smart.
但是  我希望我的生活我做主
But... I need to live my life my way.
好吧
All right.
不过这不表示我不再担心
But that doesn't mean I'm gonna stop worrying.
不表示我不再关心
It doesn't mean I'm gonna stop caring or...
我还是会不时地提醒你
reminding you from time to time
你真的  做错了
that you are, indeed... wrong.
我希望你担心  关心  提醒
And I wouldn't want you to.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我为什么还要过来
Why did I have to come back here?
因为你没有告诉我们实情  坎迪斯
Because you didn't tell us the whole story, Candice.
博阿离开后12秒
12 seconds after Beau left,
你走向了同一个方向
you headed off in the same direction.
我没有跟着他
Well, I didn't follow him, if that's what you're trying to say.
那你去哪了
Then where did you go?
记不得了  回舞池了
I don't remember. Um, back out on the dance floor.
坎迪斯  你在撒谎
Candice, you're lying.
我知道视频的事
I know about the video,
你跟博阿的视频
the one with you and Beau.
请你别告诉我父亲
Please don't tell my father.
我尽量
I'm gonna do my best not to.
我让步了  你也得有点表示
I need you to meet me halfway, though.
博阿在勒索你  对不对
Beau was blackmailing you, wasn't he?
所以你当晚在场
That's why you were there last night
所以你才杀了他
and that's why you killed him.
不  你不明白
No, you-- you don't understand.
我觉得我明白
I think I do.
你是幼儿园教师
You're a kindergarten teacher.
你知道那视频会害你丢了饭碗
You knew that that video would cost you your job
和名誉
and your reputation,
更不必说你父亲的名誉
not to mention your dad's reputation,
然后你失控了
and you lost control.
陪审团会同情你的
Any jury's gonna sympathize with you.
我也会帮你跟检察官求情
And I can put in a good word with the D.A.
但你要告诉我到底发生了什么
I just need you to tell me exactly what happened.
我要求跟我的律师谈谈
Um, I-I'd like to speak to my attorney.
法官批准了搜查令
The judge granted us the warrant.
弟兄们已经去了坎迪斯家了
The boys are on their way to Candice's
看看能不能找到
to see if they can find proof
博阿勒索她的证据
that Beau was blackmailing her.
很难过吧
It's hard, isn't it,
比起被害人  凶手竟是品行更好的人
when the killer turns out to be a better person than the victim?
我女儿在哪里
Where's my daughter?
我的律师说你们把她拘留了
My attorney says you're holding her.
我要见我女儿
I want to talk to my daughter.
阿姆斯特朗先生  你应该知道
Mr. Armstrong, you should know that Candice
坎迪斯是博阿·兰道夫谋杀案的嫌疑人
is a person of interest in the Beau Randolph case.
什么  别说笑了
What? Don't be ridiculous.
我们还是私下谈吧
We should talk about this privately.
请
Go ahead.
全都是荒谬的误会
This is all some kind of hideous mistake.
坎迪斯不会伤害任何人的
Candice wouldn't hurt anyone.
你知道
Were you aware of any...
她和博阿之间的关系吗
connection between her and Beau?
跟博阿·兰道夫之间的关系
A connection with Beau Randolph?
开玩笑吗
Are you joking?
顺便说一句  我家坎迪斯
And by the way, my Candice
才不会在夜店被逮个正着
would never be caught dead in that club.
其实  死了的是博阿[caught dead双关]
Actually, it was Beau that was caught dead.
坎迪斯当时在夜店
And Candice was in that club.
她在那种地方干什么
What on earth was she doing in this place?
或许她想保护自己不受博阿骚扰
Maybe she was trying to protect herself from Beau.
或者保护你
Or protect you.
我明确表示过不喜欢他
I made my feelings about him very plain.
我只想终止他的活动
My goal was simply to stop his activities.
从来没想过让他受到伤害
I never intended for him to get hurt.
你们觉得我的...
Do you think that my, uh...
我说的话  我的行为
My words, my--my mission...
会让坎迪斯做出什么可怕的事情吗
could have led Candice to do something terrible?
这可能吗
Is that possible?
如果我是坎迪斯  我会那么做
If I were in Candice's shoes, I would've done the same thing.
我同情她  真的
Well, I mean, I feel for her, I do.
但她知道自己惹上的是什么
But she knew what she was getting into.
她知道博阿会勒索她  所以这是她的错吗
She knew Beau would blackmail her, so this is her fault?
看看她父亲做的事
With what her dad did,
她知道博阿是什么样的人
she must have known who Beau was
知道他是干什么的
and what he was about.
跟斯嘉丽不一样
It's not like it was with Scarlet.
懂了  扯上你自己了  好吧
Oh, I see. So this is about you. Okay.
那妞确实没有如实交代  兄弟
Hey, that chick totally misrepresented herself, bro.
不过她真辣  对吧
She was hot, though, right?
对你来说  可悲的是
Here's the sad thing-- for you,
她没有如实供述
the fact that she misrepresented herself
在你看来  把她显得更性感
makes her even hotter.
不  她已经性感至极了
No, she can't be any hotter than she already is.
来看看这个
Oh, check this out.
博阿发给坎迪斯的电邮
Hmm? It is an e-mail to Candice
还带了附件
from Beau with an attachment.
可能是勒索金额
Probably the terms of the blackmail.
博阿保守性爱视频的秘密
What did Beau want in exchange
是为了交换什么呢
for keeping a lid on that sex tape?
不不  这是信托
No, no, no. This is some kind of trust,
博阿设了五百万美金
set up by Beau for $5 million.
这说不通啊
Well, that makes no sense.
如果他在勒索她
If he was blackmailing her,
为什么反而给她钱呢
why would he be giving her money?
信托不是给坎迪斯的
The trust isn't for Candice.
受益人登记的是JD·梅菲尔德
The beneficiary is listed as a "J.D. Mayfield."
在她家里没找到叫JD·梅菲尔德的人
I didn't find a J.D. Mayfield in her family.
可能是无名氏
Could be a john doe or a jane doe.
看看这个
Yo, check this out.
坎迪斯的日程表里
In Candice's date book,
几天前标了一次超声波检查
It's an ultrasound dated just a few days ago,
病人登记的是C. 梅菲尔德
and the patient is listed as a "C. Mayfield."
坎迪斯怀孕了
So Candice is pregnant.
博阿给她孩子设了信托
And Beau set up the trust for her baby,
他为什么要这么做
and why would he do that?
因为那也是他的孩子
Because it's his kid.
我在酒吧遇见了博阿
I met Beau at a bar.
觉得他风趣又可爱
I thought he was funny and cute.
我不知道他是谁
I had no idea who he was.
我也很肯定他同样不知道我是谁
I'm pretty sure he didn't know who I was, either.
时运不佳的一对
Star-crossed lovers,
就像罗密欧与朱丽叶
just like Romeo and Juliet.
前提是  罗密欧和朱丽叶喝多了
If Romeo and Juliet had gotten drunk
还发生了一夜情
and had a meaningless one-night stand.
有理
Point taken.
当我发现自己怀孕了
When I found out I was pregnant,
我意识到告诉他才是正确的做法
I knew letting him know was the right thing to do.
我觉得他根本不会在意
I mean, I figured he wouldn't care,
然后告诉我自己去解决
that he would tell me I was on my own.
即便那样我也会接受
And I would've been fine with that.
但当我给他看第一张超声波图片时
But when I showed him that first ultrasound,
他激动得快哭了
he got so choked up.
这发生在什么时候
When was this?
两个月前吧
About two months ago.
那时他和蒂芙尼分了手
That's when he broke it off with Tiffany
并对小青蛙公司产生了兴趣
and when he got interested in Little Frog Enterprises.
他准备金盆洗手  走上了正途
He was cleaning up his act, going legit.
差不多吧
Pretty much.
我以为这一切都是装的
I thought it was all an act.
但是他一直打给我
But he called all the time.
他说他真的想成为孩子生活的一部分
He said he really wanted to be a part of the child's life.
但你知道你爸爸会不同意的
But you knew your father would disapprove.
他同意的事情没有几件
My father disapproves about most things.
但这次是我
It was me.
是我不想要博阿出现的
I was the one that didn't want Beau around.
我的意思是  他名声不好
I mean, not with his reputation.
我不想连累到我的孩子
I didn't want that for my baby.
博阿不愿放弃
Beau wouldn't give up.
他告诉我
You know, he told me that
他终其一生都在寻找
all his life, he'd been searching,
追求人生的意义
and he was looking for meaning in his life,
而他最终找到了
and that he'd finally found it.
是成为一位父亲
It was being a father.
他一直告诉我他会说服我
He kept telling me that he would convince me,
他会改的
that he could change.
你那晚为什么去酒吧
Why'd you go to the club that night?
是博阿让我去的
Beau asked me to meet him there.
他想告诉我他关闭了自己的生意
He wanted to tell me that he was shutting down his business.
他把生意卖了
He was selling it?
不  他把它彻底结束了
No, he was shutting it down for good.
他说他知道这是让我相信的唯一方法
He said he knew that was the only way to convince me.
所以光盘和网站都消失了
So the DVDs, the website, it was all going away.
他有没有告诉过其他人他结束生意的计划
Did he tell anyone else that he planned on shutting it down?
是的
Yes, he did.
事实上  就在当晚
That night, in fact.
好了  好了  姑娘们  准备好了吗
Okay, okay, all right, girls. You ready?
我们去那里拍片
We're gonna take a little bit of tape
等着工作人员就位
right up here while the crew sets up.
快点  起来起来
Come on. Up, up, up.
节目还要继续对吧  特洛伊
Well, the show must go on, right, Troy?
总不能因老板的死
Can't let a little thing like the death of your boss
就耽误了狂欢
get in the way of a party.
听着  我想念博阿  他是个好朋友
Look, I miss Beau. He was a good friend.
但这就是生意
But this is a business.
我们有片子要拍要卖
Okay, we have videos to produce, distribution deals.
这不是说完就完的
This doesn't just end.
我通过让狂欢继续来纪念他
Okay, look, I honor his memory by keeping the party going.
那太好了
Oh, that's nice.
但是如果你真想纪念他
Except if you really wanted to honor his memory,
就应该关闭所有的经营
you would shut down the entire operation.
关闭
Shut it down?
我们知道博阿告诉你
We know that Beau told you
他打算彻底关闭公司
he was folding the company for good.
这太扯了
That's crazy.
是啊  你也或许是这么想的
Yeah, and you probably thought so, too.
所以你决定不能让这事发生
That's why you decided that you couldn't let it happen.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
当我们发现你有犯罪动机时
When we found out you had motive,
我们看了你的录影带
We took a look at your footage.
那你就看到我一整晚都在录影
Yeah, and you saw that I was filming all night,
包括博阿被害的时候
including while Beau was being killed.
其实是你的摄像机在录影
Actually, your camera was filming,
而你没有
but you weren't.
一般来说手持摄像机的影像
Normally the footage from a hand-held camera
是不稳定的
would be in motion.
而你的也是不稳定的
And yours was in motion,
除了11:50到11:58之间
except for from 11:50 to 11:58--
而那时博阿正前往卫生间
About the time Beau headed to the bathroom.
在这八分钟里
For those eight minutes,
影像却是稳定的
The footage was rock-steady.
你把你的摄像机放在了三脚架上
You put your camera on a tripod
之后就走开了
and you walked away.
你让它继续工作
You left it running,
是因为你知道它会给你不在场证明
knowing that that would give you an alibi.
是  我是用三脚架了
I mean, yeah, I used a tripod,
但这并不能说明我杀了他
but that doesn't prove I killed him.
是  但是凶器上的DNA却可以说明
No, but the DNA on the murder weapon will.
DNA
DNA?
我们拿到了法令对比你的DNA
We got a court order to test it against yours.
狂欢结束了  特洛伊
Party's over, Troy.
他答应我会有一天让我接手
He promised me I would take over the business someday,
答应让我发财
promised he'd get me rich,
然后他决定结束一切
and then he just decides to end it all,
决定耍我
decides to screw me over
就因为什么孩子
because of, uh, what, some baby?
得了吧
Come on.
你怎么会放弃这一切
How can you give up all this?
你会找到答案的
You're about to find out.
拷上
Cuff him.
转过去
Turn around.
所以这就是博阿被害的原因
So that's why Beau was killed,
因为钱
over money?
恐怕是的
Yeah, I'm afraid so.
但是你应该知道他没有骗你
But you should know that what he told you was the truth.
他真的在成为一个更好的人
He really was trying to be a better man.
我只是伤心孩子没有机会见到他
I'm just sad that our baby will never get to meet him.
但是总有一天  我会告诉她爸爸的故事
But one day, I'll tell her his story--
博阿是如何全兴全意做她父亲的
How beau gave his life to be her father.
那你怀得是女孩了
So you're having a daughter, then?
是
Yeah.
太棒了  恭喜
That's wonderful. Congratulations.
谢谢
Thank you.
我想你爸来看你了
I think your dad's here to see you.
我应该告诉他发生了什么
I guess I should tell him what's going on.
谢谢你
Thank you
找出了真相
for finding out the truth.
你觉得他会接受自己的外孙女吗
You think he'll be able to accept his grandchild?
一定会的
Absolutely.
你怎么那么确定
What makes you sure?
因为爸爸可以为女儿做任何事
Because a father would do anything for his daughter.